Guide to the Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel Audiovisual Materials, 1956-2018 RL.10006_AV RL.10006_AV
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Interviews, 1974-2017; 347 items
  - Broadcast video interviews, 1974-1994; 152 items
    - Joel Meyerowitz, Visions and Images: American Photographers on Photography, 1981; 00:30:46 (Box AV-015, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0218)
    - Duane Michals, Visions and Images: American Photographers on Photography, 1981; 00:29:38 (Box AV-015, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0227)
    - Charles Moore, American Architecture Now, 1980; 00:57:12 (Box AV-014, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0210)
    - Barbara Morgan, Visions and Images: American Photographers on Photography, 1981; 00:30:41 (Box AV-005, Video-cassette RL10006-Umatic-0074)
    - Robert Motherwell, Inside New York's Art World, 1977; 00:57:40 (Box AV-015, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0221_0327)
    - Alice Neel, Inside New York's Art World, 1978; 00:57:48 (Box AV-011, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0164)
    - Louise Nevelson, Inside New York's Art World, 1977; 00:28:52 (Box AV-013, Video-cassette RL10006-Umatic-0313)
    - Louise Nevelson, Barbaralee Diamonstein and …, 1978; 00:30:23 (Box AV-003, Video-cassette RL10006-Umatic-0039_02)
    - Louise Nevelson, About the Arts, 1978; 00:29:25 (Box AV-052, Video-cassette RL10006-VHS-0047_02)
    - Arnold Newman, Visions and Images: American Photographers on Photography, 1981; 00:29:03 (Box AV-013, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0196)
    - Edwin Newman, About the Arts, 1977; 00:29:17 (Box AV-001, Video-cassette RL10006-Umatic-0011_01)
    - Albert and Pearl Nipon, Inside Fashion, 1984; 00:25:57 (Box AV-022, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0332)
    - Kenneth Noland and Diane Waldman, About the Arts, 1977; 00:29:25 (Box AV-003, Video-cassette RL10006-Umatic-0040_02)
    - Richard Oldenburg, Inside New York's Art World, 1978; 01:23:53 (Box AV-008, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0112, Box AV-004, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0059, Box AV-074, Video-cassette RL10006-VHS-0251, Box AV-017, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0246)
    - Albert Paley, Handmade in America, 1982; 00:24:03 (Box AV-007, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0098)
    - Alan Sagner, Fred Papert, Barbaralee Diamonstein and …, 1978; 00:29:38 (Box AV-067, Video-cassette RL10006-VHS-0174)
    - Joseph Papp, Barbaralee Diamonstein and …, 1978; 00:29:45 (Box AV-014, Video-cassette RL10006-Umatic-0206_02)
    - Estelle Parsons, Barbaralee Diamonstein and …, 1976; 00:29:20 (Box AV-003, Video-cassette RL10006-Umatic-0040_01)
    - I.M. Pei, Inside New York's Art World, 1978; 00:36:43 (Box AV-023, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0378)
    - I.M. Pei, American Architecture Now, 1980; 01:30:04 (Box AV-014, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0211, Box AV-010, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0146)
    - Cesar Pelli, American Architecture Now, 1980; 01:18:21 (Box AV-019, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0280_0276)
    - Michael Pittas, American Architecture Now, 1983; 01:30:03 (Box AV-052, Video-cassette RL10006-VHS-0043)
    - Warren Platner, Interior Design: The New Freedom, 1981; 00:30:14 (Box AV-002, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0024)
    - James Polshek, American Architecture Now, 1980; 01:24:42 (Box AV-019, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0277_0279)
    - Robert Rauschenburg, Leo Castelli, Inside New York's Art World, 1977; 00:28:16 (Box AV-003, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0042)
    - Larry Rivers, Inside New York's Art World, 1978; 00:29:11 (Box AV-007, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0093)
    - Kevin Roche, American Architecture Now, 1984; 00:25:49 (Box AV-011, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0161)
    - James Rosenquist, Leo Castelli, Inside New York's Art World, 1978; 00:25:29 (Box AV-022, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0328)
    - Richard Roud, Wim Wenders, About the Arts, 1977; 00:28:50 (Box AV-003, Video-cassette RL10006-Umatic-0033_02)
    - Robert Ryman, Inside New York's Art World, 1977; 01:00:41 (Box AV-015, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0220)
    - John Saladino, Interior Design: The New Freedom, 1981; 00:29:32 (Box AV-013, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0195)
    - Dr. Lee Salk, Barbaralee Diamonstein and …, 1979; 00:30:17 (Box AV-006, Video-cassette RL10006-Umatic-0077_01)
    - Richard Salomon, Barbaralee Diamonstein and …, 1978; 00:29:31 (Box AV-016, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0232_02)
    - Lucas Samaras, Grace Glueck, Inside New York's Art World, 1978; 01:22:46 (Box AV-005, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0062, Box AV-015, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0217, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0216, Box AV-014, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0203)
    - Lucas Samaras, Inside New York's Art World, 1979; 00:57:37 (Box AV-015, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0179)
    - Arnold Scaasi, Fashion: The Inside Story, 1984; 00:24:58 (Box AV-017, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0255)
    - Robert Venturi, Denise Scott Brown, American Architecture Now, 1984; 00:25:40 (Box AV-026, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0388)
    - George Segal, Inside New York's Art World, 1977; 00:29:30 (Box AV-012, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0173)
    - Ronaldus Shamask, Fashion: The Inside Story, 1984; 00:25:00 (Box AV-006, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0082)
    - Frederick Sommer, Visions and Images: American Photographers on Photography, 1981; 00:28:48 (Box AV-013, Video-cassette RL10006-Umatic-0192)
    - Raphael Soyer, Inside New York's Art World, 1979; 00:59:55 (Box AV-004, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0060)
    - Robert A.M. Stern, Interior Design: The New Freedom, 1981; 00:30:27 (Box AV-002, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0021)
    - Ellen Stewart, Barbaralee Diamonstein and …, 1979; 00:29:06 (Box AV-024, Video-cassette RL10006-Umatic-0338_02)
    - Lisa Taylor, Cooper Hewitt Museum, Inside New York's Art World, circa 1978; 01:11:00 (Box AV-004, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0046_0047_0048_0049)
    - Benjamin C. Thompson, American Architecture Now, 1984; 00:25:28 (Box AV-011, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0159)
    - Stanley Tigerman, American Architecture Now II, 1984; 00:25:20 (Box AV-007, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0096)
    - Pauline Trigere, Inside Fashion, 1984; 00:25:01 (Box AV-016, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0237)
    - Massimo and Lella Vignelli, Interior Design: The New Freedom, 1981; 00:31:22 (Box AV-008, Video-cassette RL10006-UMATIC-0113)
    - Edward Villella, Barbaralee Diamonstein and …, 1978; 00:29:03 (Box AV-002, Video-cassette RL10006-Umatic-0027)
    - Theodore H. White, Barbaralee Diamonstein and …, undated; 00:29:17 (Box AV-006, Video-cassette RL10006-Umatic-0079_02)
    - Tom Wicker, Barbaralee Diamonstein and …, 1978; 00:29:40 (Box AV-047, Video-cassette RL10006-VHS-0025)
    - Garry Winogrand, Visions and Images: American Photographers on Photography, 1981; 00:30:40 (Box AV-010, Video-cassette RL10006-Umatic-0139)
  - Audio interviews, 1974-2001; 189 items
    The Audio interviews, 1974-2001, subseries is comprised mainly of interviews, conducted by Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel, for use in her books Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, and Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein. Also included are other interviews and programs that were not identified as being part of these projects but are similar in content. The audio in this subseries has been digitized and may be requested for onsite use.
    - Edward Albee, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:18 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0008_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615997)
    - Edward Albee, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:16 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0008_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615999)
    - Edward Albee, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:03 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0035_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615881)
    - Edward Albee, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:46:54 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0035_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615884)
    - Edward Albee, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:00:10 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0036_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616065)
    - Madeline Albright, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1997; 00:16:59 (Box AV-054, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0227_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615964)
    - Ellen Baker, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, circa 1995; 00:01:37 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0051_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615923)
    - Ellen Baker, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, circa 1995; 00:47:19 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0052_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616024)
    - Ellen Baker, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, circa 1995; 00:25:07 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0052_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616022)
    - Ellen Baker, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, circa 1995; 00:46:57 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0009_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615915)
    - Ellen Baker, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, circa 1995; 00:25:07 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0009_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615917)
    - Ellen Baker, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, circa 1995; 00:01:31 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0010_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616018)
    - Geoffrey Beene, Miscellaneous Interviews, undated; 00:58:28 (Box AV-048, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0112_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616001)
    - Gail Bird, Yazzi Johnson, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1981; 00:45:50 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0081_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615906)
    - Gail Bird, Yazzi Johnson, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1981; 00:45:53 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0081_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615904)
    - Gail Bird, Yazzi Johnson, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1981; 00:45:55 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0082_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615885)
    - Gail Bird, Yazzi Johnson, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1981; 00:37:31 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0082_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615888)
    - Victoria Borus, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1983; 01:02:48 (Box AV-051, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0185_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616004)
    - Victoria Borus, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1983; 00:26:37 (Box AV-051, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0185_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616006)
    - Bob Bray, Mike Schaible, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1982; 00:06:12 (Box AV-051, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0182_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616056)
    - Bob Bray, Mike Schaible, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1982; 00:00:13 (Box AV-051, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0182_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616058)
    - Carter Brown, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:14 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0018_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616180)
    - Carter Brown, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:18 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0018_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616178)
    - Carter Brown, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:25:22 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0019_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616239)
    - Denise Scott Brown, Robert Venturi, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:05:17 (Box AV-048, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0121_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616089)
    - Denise Scott Brown, Robert Venturi, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:20 (Box AV-061, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0312_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615978)
    - Denise Scott Brown, Robert Venturi, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:20 (Box AV-061, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0312_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615980)
    - Denise Scott Brown, Robert Venturi, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:11:12 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0013_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615981)
    - Denise Scott Brown, Robert Venturi, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:11 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0014_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615925)
    - Denise Scott Brown, Robert Venturi, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:26 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0014_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615927)
    - Denise Scott Brown, Robert Venturi, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:11 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0015_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615971)
    - Denise Scott Brown, Robert Venturi, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:17 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0055_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616087)
    - Denise Scott Brown, Robert Venturi, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:11:10 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0056_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615977)
    - Denise Scott Brown, Robert Venturi, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:46:58 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0057_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616055)
    - Denise Scott Brown, Robert Venturi, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:46:53 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0057_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616057)
    - Helen Gurley Brown, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:05 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0007_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615992)
    - Helen Gurley Brown, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:35:47 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0007_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615990)
    - Helen Gurley Brown, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:14 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0033_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615869)
    - Helen Gurley Brown, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:36:04 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0033_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615872)
    - Jimmy Carter, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:41:40 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0002_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616036)
    - Jimmy Carter, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:41:31 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0031_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616066)
    - Wendell Castel, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1981; 00:45:33 (Box AV-061, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0296_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616071)
    - Wendell Castel, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1981; 00:14:08 (Box AV-061, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0296_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616072)
    - Leo Castelli, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:11:11 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0048_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616207)
    - Leo Castelli, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, undated; 00:00:27 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0049_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616185)
    - Leo Castelli, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, undated; 00:31:14 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0050_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616206)
    - Leo Castelli, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, undated; 00:31:08 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0050_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616208)
    - Leo Castelli, Public Policy and the Arts, undated; 00:31:13 (Box AV-060, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0276_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615910)
    - Leo Castelli, Robert Mayer, James Rosenquist, Public Policy and the Arts, undated; 00:30:09 (Box AV-060, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0279_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615891)
    - Leo Castelli, Robert Mayer, James Rosenquist, Public Policy and the Arts, undated; 00:30:08 (Box AV-060, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0279_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615893)
    - Dale Chihuly, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1992; 00:30:09 (Box AV-049, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0150_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616074)
    - Dale Chihuly, Miscellaneous Interviews, undated; 00:37:47 (Box AV-049, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0149_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616025)
    - Christo and Jeanne-Claude, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:24 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0040_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616226)
    - Christo and Jeanne-Claude, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:24:21 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0040_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616227)
    - Christo and Jeanne-Claude, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:12 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0041_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616164)
    - Christo and Jeanne-Claude, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:23 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0041_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616166)
    - Francesco Clemente, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:30 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0024_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616181)
    - Francesco Clemente, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:20 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0024_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616179)
    - Chuck Close, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 01:03:23 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0014_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616193)
    - Chuck Close, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:29:22 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0014_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616191)
    - Chuck Close, Kinshasha Holman Conwill, Philippe de Montebello, Adam Gopnik, Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel, David Ross, Kirk Varnedoe, Inside of New York's Art World, 1994; 00:43:06 (Box AV-072, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0320_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616013)
    - Chuck Close, Kinshasha Holman Conwill, Philippe de Montebello, Adam Gopnik, Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel, David Ross, Kirk Varnedoe, Inside of New York's Art World, 1994; 00:44:56 (Box AV-072, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0320_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616012)
    - Chuck Close, Kinshasha Holman Conwill, Philippe de Montebello, Adam Gopnik, Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel, David Ross, Kirk Varnedoe, Inside of New York's Art World, 1994; 00:24:30 (Box AV-072, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0321_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616078)
    - Chuck Close, Kinshasha Holman Conwill, Philippe de Montebello, Adam Gopnik, Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel, David Ross, Kirk Varnedoe, Inside of New York's Art World, undated; 00:01:38 (Box AV-072, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0326_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615919)
    - William Conway, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:16 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0022_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615987)
    - William Conway, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:17:24 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0022_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615986)
    - William Conway, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:00:13 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0023_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616075)
    - William Conway, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:10 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0024_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616037)
    - William Conway, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:15 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0040_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616007)
    - William Conway, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:03:40 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0040_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616005)
    - William Conway, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, circa 1995; 00:47:08 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0038_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615922)
    - William Conway, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, circa 1995; 00:17:19 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0038_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615921)
    - William Conway, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, circa 1995; 00:00:11 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0039_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616040)
    - Kinshasha Holman Conwill, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:29 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0028_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616165)
    - Kinshasha Holman Conwill, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:17 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0028_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616163)
    - Kinshasha Holman Conwill, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:26 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0029_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616218)
    - Alex Cooper, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 00:31:32 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0072_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615896)
    - Alex Cooper, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 00:31:33 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0072_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615899)
    - Alex Cooper, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 00:31:25 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0073_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616026)
    - Alex Cooper, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 00:31:28 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0073_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616028)
    - Douglas Cramer, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, undated; 00:47:09 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0002_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616210)
    - Douglas Cramer, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, undated; 00:29:13 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0002_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616209)
    - Douglas Cramer, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, undated; 00:02:02 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0006_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616177)
    - D'Amboise, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 00:46:08 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0087_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616009)
    - D'Amboise, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 00:46:09 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0087_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616011)
    - Philippe de Montebello, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:18 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0026_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616234)
    - Philippe de Montebello, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:21 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0026_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616232)
    - Philippe de Montebello, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:15:31 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0027_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616170)
    - Louis Dell'Olio, Donna Karan, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 01:03:12 (Box AV-049, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0156_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615920)